<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CTFA on Taipei City FC Test Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/categories/ctfa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CTFA on Taipei City FC Test Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/ctfa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>City beat Fritz to go Top</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-beat-fritz-to-go-top/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-beat-fritz-to-go-top/</guid>
      <description>Time: 7pm, January 9th, 2010 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park
By Alice Davis and Michael Christie
With lashings of rain for a week beforehand, some doubted if the game would go ahead. But the skies cleared on Friday afternoon, so it was surprisingly warm and dry when the top two teams of the BML took to the field at 7pm on Saturday evening. The preparations were good by all the City players, Dan and Ross gave a serious team talk before the game which was just what everybody needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calvert fires City to Opening Day Victory</title>
      <link>http://example.org/calvert-fires-city-to-opening-day-victory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/calvert-fires-city-to-opening-day-victory/</guid>
      <description>Time: 10am, November 1, 2009 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park
Conditions: Wet
By Michael Christie
With an excellent squad assembled for the 2009/2010 BML season, the management team of Dan Calvert and Ross Conlon had a difficult job naming a starting eleven for the opening game. They decided on Dale Neal in goal, a three-man defence of Tim Murphy, Yunusa Njie and Matt Wharton, with Steven Raymond and Ross Conlon on the flanks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another win for Taipei City</title>
      <link>http://example.org/another-win-for-taipei-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/another-win-for-taipei-city/</guid>
      <description>Ah yes, the early BML kickoff. On one hand it makes it a bit difficult to plan wicked Saturday night festivities, yet on the other hand you&amp;rsquo;ve got still got the rest of your Sunday to do with as you please.
Both teams looked short on players during warm up. After the lineup and friendly greeting, City only had 10 guys on the field when the kickoff whistle blew.
About 15 minutes later, with a full eleven on the pitch, things started to warm up for Taipei City offensively.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
