<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>taipei football on Taipei City FC Test Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/taipei-football/</link>
    <description>Recent content in taipei football on Taipei City FC Test Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 03:28:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/taipei-football/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>City Finish In Style</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-finish-in-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 03:28:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-finish-in-style/</guid>
      <description>Time: 3pm, May 27th, 2012 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie Were the celebrations following Taipei City’s draw against Bulien premature? Had Taipei City clinched the title or was it going to be taken away at the last? Following Fritz’s victory over the Red Lions on Thursday evening, Taipei City needed a draw or win to win the BML title outright on points in the last round of the 2011-12 season, against Fritz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Fight to the Draw</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-fight-to-the-draw/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 05:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-fight-to-the-draw/</guid>
      <description>Time: 3pm, May 20th, 2012 Venue: BaiLing Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie A single point would be enough to claim a third BML Championship, but against Bulien anything might happen and what a day for a football match! On a waterlogged pitch fit only for crabs, ducks and other wildlife, Taipei City took on an old bete noire in an ugly-tempered game. The weather, pitch and the football were all equally ugly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Prevail in Weekend Double Header</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-prevail-in-weekend-double-header/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2012 08:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-prevail-in-weekend-double-header/</guid>
      <description>Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie Two games in two days is not recommended for a footballer&amp;rsquo;s health or for his play, yet, with four games left to play and firmly seated in the driver&amp;rsquo;s seat with all eyes on the prize of the BML Title, that was what was required of Taipei City against the rookie boys of San Chung High School on Saturday, May 12th and against the redoubtable Red Lions on Sunday, May 13th.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fritz Exact a Draw</title>
      <link>http://example.org/fritz-exact-a-draw/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 03:36:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/fritz-exact-a-draw/</guid>
      <description>Time: 5pm, March 25th, 2012 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie Two games of football in the space of twenty-four hours is a punishing schedule no matter what level of the game you play. If Fritz was going to get a result against Taipei City, this was a good opportunity. A few important players were missing, including Alex Ramirez and Omar Senoussi, as the Taipei City players gathered at Bai Ling on an exceptionally warm afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cushty against Mitsukoshi</title>
      <link>http://example.org/cushty-against-mitsukoshi-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 03:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/cushty-against-mitsukoshi-2/</guid>
      <description>Time: 7pm, March 24th, 2012 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie In unseasonably cold weather, Taipei City took on Mitsukoshi in the first game of the weekend double-header. Rightly concentrating on the here and now, Dan Calvert asked his squad before kick-off to forget about Fritz the next day and just do their best to beat Mitsukoshi, a team capable of surprises. Dan named a 4-4-2 formation of Dale Neal in goal; Ricardo Abrego, Brian McGuinness, Tom Clarke and ‘Dapper’ Danny Wilkinson at the back; Danny Weir, Ebu Njie, debutant Michael Crossley and Omar Malcolm in midfield; and, Brian Fitzpatrick and Dan Calvert up front.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taipei Overcome Toughest Hurdle Yet</title>
      <link>http://example.org/taipei-overcome-toughest-hurdle-yet-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 07:46:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/taipei-overcome-toughest-hurdle-yet-comments/</guid>
      <description>biuro-rachunkowe-warszawa.biz.pl - Sep 6, 2014
Providing you are a Director or employee of a company, these payments are an allowable deduction against the Corporation tax liability of the company. The Authority - Any one who has legal power over you is the Authority. For example, if your business is into plants, then you can have a Venus fly trap design for your folded business card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taipei Overcome Toughest Hurdle Yet</title>
      <link>http://example.org/taipei-overcome-toughest-hurdle-yet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 07:46:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/taipei-overcome-toughest-hurdle-yet/</guid>
      <description>Time: 7pm, March 17th, 2012 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie As usual against Hong Ming Bulien, Taipei City did not enjoy the best preparation in the critical hour leading up to the kick-off. Several players struggled to arrive in time, but Taipei City still had a good eleven ready to start, and of course an exceptionally strong bench. The 4-4-2 formation comprised Dale Neal in goal; a back line of Ricardo Abrego, Brian McGuinness, Tom Clarke and Mamadi Colley; a midfield quartet of Danny Weir, Oumar Senoussi, Michael Christie and Omar Malcolm; and a front pairing of Brian Fitzpatrick and Neo King.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Take the Shine Off the Peacocks</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-take-the-shine-off-the-peacocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 06:03:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-take-the-shine-off-the-peacocks/</guid>
      <description>Time: 2pm, March 4th, 2012 Venue: Yingfeng Riverside Park By Michael Christie On a bright, hot day at Da Jia Yingfeng Riverside Park, the Taipei City players gathered in readiness for the match against the Taipei Peacocks – on their home turf. The surface was dry and smooth in spite of the damp weather since Chinese New Year. The wind affected the flight of the ball during the game! This was the first day of BML competition in March, and the fixtures are not yet half completed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Tames Lions</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-tames-lions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 16:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-tames-lions/</guid>
      <description>Time: 10am, February 12th, 2012 Venue:BaiLing Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie Another hot weekend came around on the heels of a cold, grey week, and at 10am on Sunday morning the sun was shining bright for the long-awaited encounter between Taipei City and the Red Lions. Unlike in more temperate climes, if the sun is out in Taiwan it is already hot enough at 10am to stymie all but the fittest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Overpower the San Chung Boys</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-overpower-the-san-chung-boys/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 03:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-overpower-the-san-chung-boys/</guid>
      <description>Time: 3pm, January 15th, 2012 Venue:BaiLingBridgeRiversidePark By Michael Christie On a treacherous pitch inimical to the stylish kind of game Taipei City aspires to, the boys of San Chung Senior High were looking for an upset. In the end, though, while they showed clever footwork and some pace, they lacked strength. A solid if unspectacular performance from City was enough. Dan started with a back line of Dale Neal in goal, Matt Wharton at right-back, Brian McGuinness and Tom Clarke in central defense, and Oumar Yassouf at left-back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>International Boys Test City</title>
      <link>http://example.org/international-boys-test-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 03:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/international-boys-test-city/</guid>
      <description>Time: 7pm, January 8th, 2012 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie Rescheduled to 7pm for arcane reasons unknown, the Bai Ling pitch had slightly longer to recover from the rain but it was still a wet, stodgy surface. Covered in sand, there were no puddles and it was not too slippery, but the bobbles made for some unpredictable bounces in a competitive match. Without Ross Conlon’s customary input – his focus and enthusiasm was missed – it was left to Dan Calvert to give the pre-match team talk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Enforcers Punish Rogue Boys</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-enforcers-punish-rogue-boys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 04:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-enforcers-punish-rogue-boys/</guid>
      <description>Time: 1pm, November 27th, 2011 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie On a smooth, dry Taiwanese riverside surface, two tough expat teams faced each other in the season opener.TaipeiCitywas the favorite to win, but Rogue had a new team and was looking for an upset. Wily manager Ross Conlon opted for a 4-4-1-1 formation to start. As usual, Dale was in goal. The back four, from right-back stretching to left-back, was Ricardo Abrego, Tom Clarke, Karim Cham and “Dapper” Daniel Wilkinson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Pipped at the Post</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-pipped-at-the-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2011 06:28:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-pipped-at-the-post/</guid>
      <description>Time: 6pm, March 19th, 2011 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie With everything to play for, both Taipei City and Hong Ming Bualien lined up to contest the game of the season – the BML final in all but name. Taipei City started with a 4-4-2 formation: Dale Neal in goal, Yunusa Njie at right-back, Ross Conlon at left-back, Brian McGuinness and Tom Clarke in central defense, Carlos Mayorga at right-midfield, Alex Ramirez at left-midfield, Ebrima Njie and Badou Njie in central midfield, and Dawda Fatty and Dan Calvert up front, Dawda in the hole and Dan as the target man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Grey Fritz Just Aint What They Used to be…</title>
      <link>http://example.org/old-grey-fritz-just-aint-what-they-used-to-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 02:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/old-grey-fritz-just-aint-what-they-used-to-be/</guid>
      <description>Time: 5pm, March 13th, 2011 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie On a hot, dry Saturday afternoon, City gathered a squad of twelve to take on the once mighty Fritz. In previous seasons, facing Fritz with such a small squad would have been dicing with ignominious defeat, but Fritz are not what they were. (It seems like they&amp;rsquo;ve gone downhill a lot since last season, never mind from when they were at their peak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Season So Far</title>
      <link>http://example.org/the-season-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 08:37:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/the-season-so-far/</guid>
      <description>By Michael Christie After twelve games played, with ten victories, one draw and one defeat, Taipei City face into the penultimate game of the BML season in top spot. So, how has the season actually progressed for Taipei City so far…? Read on… Game 1: An Easy Opener against JFC Taipei City was lucky to have their easiest game of the season first. New to the BML, JFC strangely decided to field a weak team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Flood of Goals on a Wettish Day</title>
      <link>http://example.org/a-flood-of-goals-on-a-wettish-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 08:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/a-flood-of-goals-on-a-wettish-day/</guid>
      <description>Time: 10am, November 7th, 2010 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie There was a nice, slick surface, if a little wet and slippery in places, at Bai Ling for when Taipei City kicked off their BML campaign against JFC on Sunday morning at 9am. The slick surface meant that the ball skidded quickly over longer distances than usual, so everything was set up for a good game between two teams that like to pass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taipei City wrap up BML season in style with win</title>
      <link>http://example.org/taipei-city-wrap-up-bml-season-in-style-with-win/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2010 03:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/taipei-city-wrap-up-bml-season-in-style-with-win/</guid>
      <description>By John Phillips Taipei Times Tuesday, Mar 30th, 2010 Taipei City FC wrapped up a successful Businessman’s League (BML) campaign with a narrow 2-1 victory over last season’s champions Fritz FC at Shilin’s Bailing Bridge on Sunday. With City having already made their second BML championship mathematically secure last week, both teams went into the season’s final game with little to play for but pride. The multinational expat side opened the scoring early in the first half with a fine solo effort from Alex Ramirez, the Mexican outpacing the Fritz defense to slide a neat finish past the ’keeper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Champions Prove their Point</title>
      <link>http://example.org/the-champions-prove-their-point/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2010 04:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/the-champions-prove-their-point/</guid>
      <description>Time: 10am, March 21st, 2010 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie On a warm morning, with a sandstorm blowing in from Mainland China, Taipei City faced Fritz Air in their penultimate game this season. Missing their influential contingent of Gambian students, City nevertheless assembled a strong eleven, albeit without regular goalkeeper, Dale (who turned up after the final whistle), obliging Spencer to put on the keeper&amp;rsquo;s jersey and gloves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Chong Raise Their Level But City Overcomes</title>
      <link>http://example.org/san-chong-raise-their-level-but-city-overcomes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2010 03:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/san-chong-raise-their-level-but-city-overcomes/</guid>
      <description>Time: 1pm, March 14th, 2010 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Ed Cartee With 3 games left in the season, City knew that 2 wins would clinch the BML title; but the way to that goal lay first through the San Chong boys, one of the more impressive possession-oriented sides in the rest of the league, so City had to be fully focused and honed in on the 90 minutes before them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amateur Soccer Leagues set for Thrilling Finales</title>
      <link>http://example.org/amateur-soccer-leagues-set-for-thrilling-finales/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 05:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/amateur-soccer-leagues-set-for-thrilling-finales/</guid>
      <description>By John Phillips Taipei Times Saturday, Mar 13, 2010 At least one of Taipei’s amateur soccer leagues will be decided tomorrow as Da-an face the Red Lions needing to win by at least three clear goals to snatch the Carnegies Premier League (CPL) title at 1pm at Taipei’s Dajia Riverside Park. Across the city at Shilin’s Bai­ling Bridge at 4pm, expat team Taipei City can take a huge step toward clinching their second Businessman’s League (BML) trophy when they take on Sanchung High School.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Get the Last Laugh</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-get-the-last-laugh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2010 08:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-get-the-last-laugh/</guid>
      <description>Time: 5.30pm, February 8th, 2010 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie Agreeing to put the start of the match back to 5.30, the match referee wasn&amp;rsquo;t very sympathetic to the eight City players kitted up at 5.25 when asked to delay it further. Still, within seconds of a 4-3-0 formation taking the field, Dawda, Tim, Mamadi, Ebou and Yunusa arrived. Niklas also showed up, but he&amp;rsquo;d lost the keys to his rooms so he didn&amp;rsquo;t have a kit and had to watch from the sidelines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Murphy Brace, City Bend But Don&#39;t Break</title>
      <link>http://example.org/murphy-brace-city-bend-but-dont-break/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 06:01:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/murphy-brace-city-bend-but-dont-break/</guid>
      <description>Time: 3pm, January 31st, 2010 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Ed Cartee The win streak is still intact as Taipei City make a run for the BML title, despite City not being their usual selves on this day. The weather was decently hot, especially in contrast to the cooler temperatures in recent weeks, and many of City&amp;rsquo;s players weren&amp;rsquo;t totally fresh since they had already played a full game earlier in the day for their CPL teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retribution for City, Rogue Run Ragged</title>
      <link>http://example.org/retribution-for-city-rogue-run-ragged/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2010 08:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/retribution-for-city-rogue-run-ragged/</guid>
      <description>Time: 1pm, January 24th, 2010 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie The last time City and Rogue met, in November, produced an upset and the only loss City have suffered this season. The Rogue were without Canadian Andy, scorer of a spectacular goal in the earlier game, but still assembled a good, determined side. For their part, the Taipei City management team of Ross and Dan urged every every player to maximize their effort levels, and only then would football skill and know-how decide the result.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Threadbare Blues have enough for Bulien</title>
      <link>http://example.org/threadbare-blues-have-more-than-enough-for-bulien/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 05:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/threadbare-blues-have-more-than-enough-for-bulien/</guid>
      <description>Time: 10am, January 17th, 2010 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By John Phillips An understrength Taipei City side overcame a spirited performance by Bulien to maintain their challenge for a second BML crown. In the end the scoreline flattered Bulien who scored their second goal with the final kick of the game and never looked likely to upset a well-drilled City side. Missing regular starters Calvert, Ramirez, Christie, Conlon, the Njie trio and both goalkeepers through a mixture of injury, suspension and other commitments, City shuffled their pack but still had enough firepower to see off a Bulien team that worked hard but rarely threatened from open play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City beat Fritz to go Top</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-beat-fritz-to-go-top/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2010 08:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-beat-fritz-to-go-top/</guid>
      <description>Time: 7pm, January 9th, 2010 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Alice Davis and Michael Christie With lashings of rain for a week beforehand, some doubted if the game would go ahead. But the skies cleared on Friday afternoon, so it was surprisingly warm and dry when the top two teams of the BML took to the field at 7pm on Saturday evening. The preparations were good by all the City players, Dan and Ross gave a serious team talk before the game which was just what everybody needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Make Light Work of Air</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-make-light-work-of-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2009 09:47:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-make-light-work-of-air/</guid>
      <description>On a cold morning,Taipei City engaged with a depleted Fritz Air team. The kick-off was put back thirty minutes to allow enough Fritz Air players to get out of bed. This was frustrating for City given that everybody had assembled right on time. Dawda led an excellent warm-up at 9.45, but the game started at about 10.30. When the game finally started, City fielded an exceptionally strong eleven against a team of eight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Chong Salvage Point</title>
      <link>http://example.org/san-chong-salvage-point/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2009 07:09:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/san-chong-salvage-point/</guid>
      <description>Time: 1pm, December 13th, 2009 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie On an extremely hot day, with the sun beating down from a high place, Taipei City kicked off against San Chong. Ross had warned everybody before the game that San Chong had recently strung together some good results against the better sides in the league, so they would not be the pushovers remembered from previous seasons. He was right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dentway Gets a Drilling</title>
      <link>http://example.org/dentway-gets-a-drilling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 17:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/dentway-gets-a-drilling/</guid>
      <description>Time: 3pm, December 6th, 2009 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie On a warm and sunny day, Taipei City easily overcame the resistance offered by Dentway but only came away with five goals. The first clean sheet of the season was possibly more important than the margin of victory, if City can build on this performance. The first half started with Alex Moga in goal; a back three of Matt Wharton, Tim Murphy and John Phillips; a five-man midfield of Spencer Pangborn and Stevey Reymond on the right and left flanks, and Oliver Harley, Michael Christie and Ebrima Njie in the middle; and, a forward pairing of Dawda Fatty and Dan Calvert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every (Under)Dog Has Its Day</title>
      <link>http://example.org/every-underdog-has-its-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 17:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/every-underdog-has-its-day/</guid>
      <description>Time: 3pm, December 5th, 2009 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Alice Davis Was there the air of over-confidence amongst the Taipei City team on Saturday afternoon? Were the players expecting Rogue FC to succumb to their playful fancy tickles, roll over, and die? Only City’s players can answer that, but one thing was evident. Rogue ain’t no poodle. Baring row after row of jagged teeth, Rogue’s seemingly (and suprisingly?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City too strong for the Mighty Shane Japan</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-too-strong-for-the-mighty-shane-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2009 08:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-too-strong-for-the-mighty-shane-japan/</guid>
      <description>Location: Taipei American School Date: Friday 26th June 8pm Starting Line-up: Dale Neal, Tim Murphy, Lar Kenny, Kyle Painter, Steven Reymond, Eddie Painter, Ebrima Njie, Badou Njie, Alex Ramirez, Dan Calvert, Gustavo Lopez Subs: Dawda Fatty for Eddie Painter. How best to describe the man with the double barreled name Neil O&amp;rsquo;Maonaigh-Lennon? Enthusiastic, passionate, mad . . . call it what you will but one thing you can’t deny is the mark he made on this island of ours in the year or so he spent here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
