<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>taipei soccer on Taipei City FC Test Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/taipei-soccer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in taipei soccer on Taipei City FC Test Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 04:20:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/taipei-soccer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>City Enforcers Punish Rogue Boys</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-enforcers-punish-rogue-boys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 04:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-enforcers-punish-rogue-boys/</guid>
      <description>Time: 1pm, November 27th, 2011 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie On a smooth, dry Taiwanese riverside surface, two tough expat teams faced each other in the season opener.TaipeiCitywas the favorite to win, but Rogue had a new team and was looking for an upset. Wily manager Ross Conlon opted for a 4-4-1-1 formation to start. As usual, Dale was in goal. The back four, from right-back stretching to left-back, was Ricardo Abrego, Tom Clarke, Karim Cham and “Dapper” Daniel Wilkinson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deaflympic soccer champs take honors against Taipei City</title>
      <link>http://example.org/deaflympic-soccer-champs-take-honors-against-taipei-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2009 01:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/deaflympic-soccer-champs-take-honors-against-taipei-city/</guid>
      <description>By Dave Carroll Taipei Times Sunday, Aug 30, 2009 The British Deaflympic men’s soccer team beat Businessman’s League champions Taipei City FC 3-0 in a warmup match in Tianmu yesterday. A 4:30pm kick off on a pitch half covered in shadow with a gentle breeze blowing were about as ideal conditions as the teams could have wished for considering the recent heat. [caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_406&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;500&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Photograph by Ashton Jean-Pierre on behalf of the BSLBT&amp;rdquo;][/caption] Taipei City, a team consisting of expats living and working in Taiwan, started the brighter and had the best of the early chances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City too strong for the Mighty Shane Japan</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-too-strong-for-the-mighty-shane-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2009 08:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-too-strong-for-the-mighty-shane-japan/</guid>
      <description>Location: Taipei American School Date: Friday 26th June 8pm Starting Line-up: Dale Neal, Tim Murphy, Lar Kenny, Kyle Painter, Steven Reymond, Eddie Painter, Ebrima Njie, Badou Njie, Alex Ramirez, Dan Calvert, Gustavo Lopez Subs: Dawda Fatty for Eddie Painter. How best to describe the man with the double barreled name Neil O&amp;rsquo;Maonaigh-Lennon? Enthusiastic, passionate, mad . . . call it what you will but one thing you can’t deny is the mark he made on this island of ours in the year or so he spent here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
