<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>deaflympics on Taipei City FC Test Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/deaflympics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in deaflympics on Taipei City FC Test Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2009 01:56:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/deaflympics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Deaflympic soccer champs take honors against Taipei City</title>
      <link>http://example.org/deaflympic-soccer-champs-take-honors-against-taipei-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2009 01:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/deaflympic-soccer-champs-take-honors-against-taipei-city/</guid>
      <description>By Dave Carroll Taipei Times Sunday, Aug 30, 2009 The British Deaflympic men’s soccer team beat Businessman’s League champions Taipei City FC 3-0 in a warmup match in Tianmu yesterday. A 4:30pm kick off on a pitch half covered in shadow with a gentle breeze blowing were about as ideal conditions as the teams could have wished for considering the recent heat. [caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_406&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;500&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Photograph by Ashton Jean-Pierre on behalf of the BSLBT&amp;rdquo;][/caption] Taipei City, a team consisting of expats living and working in Taiwan, started the brighter and had the best of the early chances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taipei City to play British Deaf Olympic Team</title>
      <link>http://example.org/taipei-city-to-play-british-deaf-olympic-team-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 05:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/taipei-city-to-play-british-deaf-olympic-team-comments/</guid>
      <description>anthony - May 5, 2011
AM THE CHAIRPERSON OF FOOTBALL IN SA AND HAS MANY FOOTBALL TEAMS. just do me a favour by find any deaf football club in ur country that is what u can help me regards
okay thanks for respond,&amp;hellip;actually am a footballer and i will to feel among you bringing to the word of God, but i have a little problem here i want come over there to come and prove my skills but i don&amp;rsquo;t enough money with, and i don&amp;rsquo;t mind if you can help me with that please okay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taipei City to play British Deaf Olympic Team</title>
      <link>http://example.org/taipei-city-to-play-british-deaf-olympic-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 05:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/taipei-city-to-play-british-deaf-olympic-team/</guid>
      <description>Written by Oliver www.waakao.com
Just ahead of Taipei&amp;rsquo;s first international sporting event, the Deaf Olympics; one of the Taipei&amp;rsquo;s premier football clubs will face off against the reigning gold medallists in the games, Great Britain. Although, the countries in the British Isles have been eluded by any kind of silverware since 1966 in World or European tournaments; in the Deaf Olympics they are champions. Great Britain&amp;rsquo;s Blind Olympic team has won in the games a total of six times and is the current champion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
