<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chinese Taipei on Taipei City FC Test Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/chinese-taipei/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chinese Taipei on Taipei City FC Test Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2010 03:42:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/chinese-taipei/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>San Chong Raise Their Level But City Overcomes</title>
      <link>http://example.org/san-chong-raise-their-level-but-city-overcomes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2010 03:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/san-chong-raise-their-level-but-city-overcomes/</guid>
      <description>Time: 1pm, March 14th, 2010 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Ed Cartee With 3 games left in the season, City knew that 2 wins would clinch the BML title; but the way to that goal lay first through the San Chong boys, one of the more impressive possession-oriented sides in the rest of the league, so City had to be fully focused and honed in on the 90 minutes before them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taipei City FC give Chinese Taipei a run for their money</title>
      <link>http://example.org/taipei-city-fc-loses-to-chinese-taipei/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 16:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/taipei-city-fc-loses-to-chinese-taipei/</guid>
      <description>After winning the 2008 BML Championship, Taipei City Football Club had the rare opportunity to play a friendly match against the Taiwanese National Team. See the Taipei Times report here. This once-in-a-lifetime chance was definitely the highlight of this amateur footballer&amp;rsquo;s career. (The Taiwan national team squad competes internationally as Chinese Taipei.) Chinese Taipei showed their impressive speed and endurance against Taipei City FC. They were fast with their passes and physically fit.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
