<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rogue on Taipei City FC Test Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/rogue/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rogue on Taipei City FC Test Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 04:20:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/rogue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>City Enforcers Punish Rogue Boys</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-enforcers-punish-rogue-boys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 04:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-enforcers-punish-rogue-boys/</guid>
      <description>Time: 1pm, November 27th, 2011 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie On a smooth, dry Taiwanese riverside surface, two tough expat teams faced each other in the season opener.TaipeiCitywas the favorite to win, but Rogue had a new team and was looking for an upset. Wily manager Ross Conlon opted for a 4-4-1-1 formation to start. As usual, Dale was in goal. The back four, from right-back stretching to left-back, was Ricardo Abrego, Tom Clarke, Karim Cham and “Dapper” Daniel Wilkinson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retribution for City, Rogue Run Ragged</title>
      <link>http://example.org/retribution-for-city-rogue-run-ragged/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2010 08:50:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/retribution-for-city-rogue-run-ragged/</guid>
      <description>Time: 1pm, January 24th, 2010 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie The last time City and Rogue met, in November, produced an upset and the only loss City have suffered this season. The Rogue were without Canadian Andy, scorer of a spectacular goal in the earlier game, but still assembled a good, determined side. For their part, the Taipei City management team of Ross and Dan urged every every player to maximize their effort levels, and only then would football skill and know-how decide the result.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every (Under)Dog Has Its Day</title>
      <link>http://example.org/every-underdog-has-its-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 17:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/every-underdog-has-its-day/</guid>
      <description>Time: 3pm, December 5th, 2009 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Alice Davis Was there the air of over-confidence amongst the Taipei City team on Saturday afternoon? Were the players expecting Rogue FC to succumb to their playful fancy tickles, roll over, and die? Only City’s players can answer that, but one thing was evident. Rogue ain’t no poodle. Baring row after row of jagged teeth, Rogue’s seemingly (and suprisingly?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taipei City takes Rogue out to lunch</title>
      <link>http://example.org/taipei-city-takes-rogue-out-to-lunch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2009 12:51:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/taipei-city-takes-rogue-out-to-lunch/</guid>
      <description>Weather: sunny and breezy with a little wind Field: hard and dry Taipei City came out strong against the boys over at Rogue FC, scoring a goal in the first 4 minutes of the game. Steve crossed to Dan for the easy put away, 1-0. Moments later another goal was in the back of the net, again from Steve crossing to Mr. Calvert again, 2-0. Later in the half Matt Swift from Rogue scored an own goal, 3-0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taipei City vs. Rogue FC</title>
      <link>http://example.org/taipei-city-vs-rogue-fc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2008 15:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/taipei-city-vs-rogue-fc/</guid>
      <description>First game of the year against BML newcomers, Rogue FC.
Taipei City won 5-1. Goal scorers were Dan Calvert with 3 and Dawda Fatty with 2.
[caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_92&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;500&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Stretching before the match.&amp;rdquo;][/caption] [caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_93&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;500&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Nice sunny day&amp;rdquo;][/caption] [caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_94&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;500&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Spencer Pangborn running down the line&amp;rdquo;][/caption] [caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_95&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;500&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Tim Murphy sends a free kick up to the forwards.&amp;rdquo;][/caption]</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
