<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>International on Taipei City FC Test Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/international/</link>
    <description>Recent content in International on Taipei City FC Test Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 03:32:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/international/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>International Boys Test City</title>
      <link>http://example.org/international-boys-test-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 03:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/international-boys-test-city/</guid>
      <description>Time: 7pm, January 8th, 2012 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie Rescheduled to 7pm for arcane reasons unknown, the Bai Ling pitch had slightly longer to recover from the rain but it was still a wet, stodgy surface. Covered in sand, there were no puddles and it was not too slippery, but the bobbles made for some unpredictable bounces in a competitive match. Without Ross Conlon’s customary input – his focus and enthusiasm was missed – it was left to Dan Calvert to give the pre-match team talk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FIFA Futsal International City Cup Taipei</title>
      <link>http://example.org/fifa-futsal-international-city-cup-taipei/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 06:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/fifa-futsal-international-city-cup-taipei/</guid>
      <description>By Michael Christie Aug 7-9th, 2010 Before I begin the report proper, let me just say why I think we were invited to the tournament. I believe we were brought in to play the role of whipping boys. We were paraded as the International Union of Brothers, but with only a couple of weeks notice we could hardly be expected to play as a well-oiled Futsal team, especially against high-level specialists in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deaflympic soccer champs take honors against Taipei City</title>
      <link>http://example.org/deaflympic-soccer-champs-take-honors-against-taipei-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2009 01:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/deaflympic-soccer-champs-take-honors-against-taipei-city/</guid>
      <description>By Dave Carroll Taipei Times Sunday, Aug 30, 2009 The British Deaflympic men’s soccer team beat Businessman’s League champions Taipei City FC 3-0 in a warmup match in Tianmu yesterday. A 4:30pm kick off on a pitch half covered in shadow with a gentle breeze blowing were about as ideal conditions as the teams could have wished for considering the recent heat. [caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_406&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;500&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Photograph by Ashton Jean-Pierre on behalf of the BSLBT&amp;rdquo;][/caption] Taipei City, a team consisting of expats living and working in Taiwan, started the brighter and had the best of the early chances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taipei City to play British Deaf Olympic Team</title>
      <link>http://example.org/taipei-city-to-play-british-deaf-olympic-team-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 05:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/taipei-city-to-play-british-deaf-olympic-team-comments/</guid>
      <description>anthony - May 5, 2011
AM THE CHAIRPERSON OF FOOTBALL IN SA AND HAS MANY FOOTBALL TEAMS. just do me a favour by find any deaf football club in ur country that is what u can help me regards
okay thanks for respond,&amp;hellip;actually am a footballer and i will to feel among you bringing to the word of God, but i have a little problem here i want come over there to come and prove my skills but i don&amp;rsquo;t enough money with, and i don&amp;rsquo;t mind if you can help me with that please okay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taipei City to play British Deaf Olympic Team</title>
      <link>http://example.org/taipei-city-to-play-british-deaf-olympic-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 05:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/taipei-city-to-play-british-deaf-olympic-team/</guid>
      <description>Written by Oliver www.waakao.com
Just ahead of Taipei&amp;rsquo;s first international sporting event, the Deaf Olympics; one of the Taipei&amp;rsquo;s premier football clubs will face off against the reigning gold medallists in the games, Great Britain. Although, the countries in the British Isles have been eluded by any kind of silverware since 1966 in World or European tournaments; in the Deaf Olympics they are champions. Great Britain&amp;rsquo;s Blind Olympic team has won in the games a total of six times and is the current champion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taipei City FC give Chinese Taipei a run for their money</title>
      <link>http://example.org/taipei-city-fc-loses-to-chinese-taipei/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2008 16:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/taipei-city-fc-loses-to-chinese-taipei/</guid>
      <description>After winning the 2008 BML Championship, Taipei City Football Club had the rare opportunity to play a friendly match against the Taiwanese National Team. See the Taipei Times report here. This once-in-a-lifetime chance was definitely the highlight of this amateur footballer&amp;rsquo;s career. (The Taiwan national team squad competes internationally as Chinese Taipei.) Chinese Taipei showed their impressive speed and endurance against Taipei City FC. They were fast with their passes and physically fit.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
