<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Friendly Game on Taipei City FC Test Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/friendly-game/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Friendly Game on Taipei City FC Test Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2009 03:55:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/friendly-game/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>City take Ming Chuan University to school</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-take-ming-chuan-university-to-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2009 03:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-take-ming-chuan-university-to-school/</guid>
      <description>by Michael Christie Venue: Ming Chuan University Campus, Tao Yuan Time: Sat Sept 5th, 4.30pm Conditions: Dry and hot Here was a game with lots of chances at both ends and generally good performances from both teams. On a dry, uneven pitch, Ming Chuan University arguably started better with their triangular passing causing problems down both flanks early on. It was from this kind of attack that they opened the scoring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taipei City to play British Deaf Olympic Team</title>
      <link>http://example.org/taipei-city-to-play-british-deaf-olympic-team-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 05:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/taipei-city-to-play-british-deaf-olympic-team-comments/</guid>
      <description>anthony - May 5, 2011
AM THE CHAIRPERSON OF FOOTBALL IN SA AND HAS MANY FOOTBALL TEAMS. just do me a favour by find any deaf football club in ur country that is what u can help me regards
okay thanks for respond,&amp;hellip;actually am a footballer and i will to feel among you bringing to the word of God, but i have a little problem here i want come over there to come and prove my skills but i don&amp;rsquo;t enough money with, and i don&amp;rsquo;t mind if you can help me with that please okay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taipei City to play British Deaf Olympic Team</title>
      <link>http://example.org/taipei-city-to-play-british-deaf-olympic-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2009 05:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/taipei-city-to-play-british-deaf-olympic-team/</guid>
      <description>Written by Oliver www.waakao.com
Just ahead of Taipei&amp;rsquo;s first international sporting event, the Deaf Olympics; one of the Taipei&amp;rsquo;s premier football clubs will face off against the reigning gold medallists in the games, Great Britain. Although, the countries in the British Isles have been eluded by any kind of silverware since 1966 in World or European tournaments; in the Deaf Olympics they are champions. Great Britain&amp;rsquo;s Blind Olympic team has won in the games a total of six times and is the current champion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City too strong for the Mighty Shane Japan</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-too-strong-for-the-mighty-shane-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2009 08:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-too-strong-for-the-mighty-shane-japan/</guid>
      <description>Location: Taipei American School Date: Friday 26th June 8pm Starting Line-up: Dale Neal, Tim Murphy, Lar Kenny, Kyle Painter, Steven Reymond, Eddie Painter, Ebrima Njie, Badou Njie, Alex Ramirez, Dan Calvert, Gustavo Lopez Subs: Dawda Fatty for Eddie Painter. How best to describe the man with the double barreled name Neil O&amp;rsquo;Maonaigh-Lennon? Enthusiastic, passionate, mad . . . call it what you will but one thing you can’t deny is the mark he made on this island of ours in the year or so he spent here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
