<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>vs. Red Lions on Taipei City FC Test Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/vs.-red-lions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in vs. Red Lions on Taipei City FC Test Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 May 2012 08:56:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/vs.-red-lions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>City Prevail in Weekend Double Header</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-prevail-in-weekend-double-header/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2012 08:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-prevail-in-weekend-double-header/</guid>
      <description>Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie Two games in two days is not recommended for a footballer&amp;rsquo;s health or for his play, yet, with four games left to play and firmly seated in the driver&amp;rsquo;s seat with all eyes on the prize of the BML Title, that was what was required of Taipei City against the rookie boys of San Chung High School on Saturday, May 12th and against the redoubtable Red Lions on Sunday, May 13th.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Tames Lions</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-tames-lions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 16:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-tames-lions/</guid>
      <description>Time: 10am, February 12th, 2012 Venue:BaiLing Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie Another hot weekend came around on the heels of a cold, grey week, and at 10am on Sunday morning the sun was shining bright for the long-awaited encounter between Taipei City and the Red Lions. Unlike in more temperate climes, if the sun is out in Taiwan it is already hot enough at 10am to stymie all but the fittest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Season So Far</title>
      <link>http://example.org/the-season-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 08:37:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/the-season-so-far/</guid>
      <description>By Michael Christie After twelve games played, with ten victories, one draw and one defeat, Taipei City face into the penultimate game of the BML season in top spot. So, how has the season actually progressed for Taipei City so far…? Read on… Game 1: An Easy Opener against JFC Taipei City was lucky to have their easiest game of the season first. New to the BML, JFC strangely decided to field a weak team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Get the Last Laugh</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-get-the-last-laugh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2010 08:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-get-the-last-laugh/</guid>
      <description>Time: 5.30pm, February 8th, 2010 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie Agreeing to put the start of the match back to 5.30, the match referee wasn&amp;rsquo;t very sympathetic to the eight City players kitted up at 5.25 when asked to delay it further. Still, within seconds of a 4-3-0 formation taking the field, Dawda, Tim, Mamadi, Ebou and Yunusa arrived. Niklas also showed up, but he&amp;rsquo;d lost the keys to his rooms so he didn&amp;rsquo;t have a kit and had to watch from the sidelines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Take the Points in Weekend Double Header</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-take-the-points-in-weekend-double-header/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2009 06:29:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-take-the-points-in-weekend-double-header/</guid>
      <description>Taipei City took six of a possible six points over the weekend with two wins in well-contested battles. Saturday saw the team face an old enemy, The Red Lions. The Lions, reinvigorated by the offseason’s most controversial signing Onur Dogan, looked lively up front and gave the City defence plenty to think about. The Turk scored two goals on the night, the second a fine finish on the turn and volley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City claim revenge on Red Lions</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-claims-revenge-on-red-lions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2009 14:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-claims-revenge-on-red-lions/</guid>
      <description>Match Report by Michael Christie Location: Bai Ling B (the crappy pitch) Conditions: Fair to firm Referee: Wearing sunglasses before the game Report: Starting in a 3-5-2 formation, Taipei City took the game to the Red Lions from the whistle. Most importantly, every forward and midfielder pushed up and put pressure on the opponent. On an uneven surface, the Lions were always on the back foot. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t easy for City to play good football either, but City succeeded in passing the ball and keeping possession.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Lions defeat Taipei City FC</title>
      <link>http://example.org/red-lions-defeat-taipei-city-fc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2008 15:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/red-lions-defeat-taipei-city-fc/</guid>
      <description>In a repeat of last year&amp;rsquo;s 1st leg of the BML, the Red Lions served up a healthy dish of revenge pie beating the reigning BML champions 2-1. The boys in blue were up 1-0 at halftime but the Red Lions fought back hard in the 2nd half to score 2 goals and take home the win. Taipei City did manage to score a goal, M. Christie in the 2nd half.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taipei City FC Defeat Red Lions to go top of the BML Standings</title>
      <link>http://example.org/taipei-city-fc-defeat-red-lions-to-go-top-of-the-bml-standings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 15:22:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/taipei-city-fc-defeat-red-lions-to-go-top-of-the-bml-standings/</guid>
      <description>Taipei City&amp;rsquo;s 6th consecutive victory, a 5-0 beating of the Red Lions, came as no surprise as the team has played steady throughout the year. The score came in quite handy, because Taipei City are now sitting on top of the league table, just ahead of Fritz on goal difference. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
