<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Southeasterly on Taipei City FC Test Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/southeasterly/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Southeasterly on Taipei City FC Test Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 05:50:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/southeasterly/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Amateur Soccer Leagues set for Thrilling Finales</title>
      <link>http://example.org/amateur-soccer-leagues-set-for-thrilling-finales/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 05:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/amateur-soccer-leagues-set-for-thrilling-finales/</guid>
      <description>By John Phillips Taipei Times Saturday, Mar 13, 2010 At least one of Taipei’s amateur soccer leagues will be decided tomorrow as Da-an face the Red Lions needing to win by at least three clear goals to snatch the Carnegies Premier League (CPL) title at 1pm at Taipei’s Dajia Riverside Park. Across the city at Shilin’s Bai­ling Bridge at 4pm, expat team Taipei City can take a huge step toward clinching their second Businessman’s League (BML) trophy when they take on Sanchung High School.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Take the Points in Weekend Double Header</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-take-the-points-in-weekend-double-header/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2009 06:29:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-take-the-points-in-weekend-double-header/</guid>
      <description>Taipei City took six of a possible six points over the weekend with two wins in well-contested battles. Saturday saw the team face an old enemy, The Red Lions. The Lions, reinvigorated by the offseason’s most controversial signing Onur Dogan, looked lively up front and gave the City defence plenty to think about. The Turk scored two goals on the night, the second a fine finish on the turn and volley.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
