<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>vs. Mitsukoshi on Taipei City FC Test Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/vs.-mitsukoshi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in vs. Mitsukoshi on Taipei City FC Test Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 03:12:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/vs.-mitsukoshi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cushty against Mitsukoshi</title>
      <link>http://example.org/cushty-against-mitsukoshi-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 03:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/cushty-against-mitsukoshi-2/</guid>
      <description>Time: 7pm, March 24th, 2012 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie In unseasonably cold weather, Taipei City took on Mitsukoshi in the first game of the weekend double-header. Rightly concentrating on the here and now, Dan Calvert asked his squad before kick-off to forget about Fritz the next day and just do their best to beat Mitsukoshi, a team capable of surprises. Dan named a 4-4-2 formation of Dale Neal in goal; Ricardo Abrego, Brian McGuinness, Tom Clarke and ‘Dapper’ Danny Wilkinson at the back; Danny Weir, Ebu Njie, debutant Michael Crossley and Omar Malcolm in midfield; and, Brian Fitzpatrick and Dan Calvert up front.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Season So Far</title>
      <link>http://example.org/the-season-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 08:37:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/the-season-so-far/</guid>
      <description>By Michael Christie After twelve games played, with ten victories, one draw and one defeat, Taipei City face into the penultimate game of the BML season in top spot. So, how has the season actually progressed for Taipei City so far…? Read on… Game 1: An Easy Opener against JFC Taipei City was lucky to have their easiest game of the season first. New to the BML, JFC strangely decided to field a weak team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Murphy Brace, City Bend But Don&#39;t Break</title>
      <link>http://example.org/murphy-brace-city-bend-but-dont-break/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 06:01:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/murphy-brace-city-bend-but-dont-break/</guid>
      <description>Time: 3pm, January 31st, 2010 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Ed Cartee The win streak is still intact as Taipei City make a run for the BML title, despite City not being their usual selves on this day. The weather was decently hot, especially in contrast to the cooler temperatures in recent weeks, and many of City&amp;rsquo;s players weren&amp;rsquo;t totally fresh since they had already played a full game earlier in the day for their CPL teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unprecedented Penalty Saves City’s Skin</title>
      <link>http://example.org/unprecedented-penalty-saves-citys-skin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2009 05:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/unprecedented-penalty-saves-citys-skin/</guid>
      <description>Time: 7.30pm, November 11, 2009 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park A cagey affair saw City edge out a resilient Shin Kong Mitsukoshi side 2-1 last Wednesday evening. In an unprecedented turn of events, the City boys had the referee to thank when they were awarded a very dubious penalty midway through the second half, at a time when neither team had yet managed to score. Mitsukoshi’s central defender was adjudged to have tugged at Dan Calvert’s jersey as he tried to get on the end of a cross from the right wing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City hands Mitsukoshi another defeat</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-hands-mitsukoshi-another-defeat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2009 17:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-hands-mitsukoshi-another-defeat/</guid>
      <description>by Michael Christie Location: Bai Ling A Time: 1pm Opposition: Mitsukoshi Conditions: very hot and humid Formation: 3-5-2 Team: Sam, Spencer, Christie, John, Steve, Chris, Tim, Alex R, Danny (Rojen (Alex D)), Gustavo, Dan. The last time Taipei City played Mitsukoshi the score was 6-2. It was the same this time. In the hot midday sun, City put together a good performance against uninspired opposition. Though not without talent in some positions, it seemed like Mitsukoshi were firmly put in their place after just a few minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taipei City sticks it to Mitsukoshi</title>
      <link>http://example.org/taipei-city-sticks-it-to-mitsukoshi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2009 16:01:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/taipei-city-sticks-it-to-mitsukoshi/</guid>
      <description>Clear day, warm, little to no wind. Alex R. scored in the first 5 minutes. Then Dawda scored 10 min later. And then again 10 minutes later. 3-0 halftime. A few changes at the half with the guys coming over from the TPL to help out. Dawda put another one in the back of the net for a hard fought hat trick on the day. Shawn also scored 2 goals with one coming from a nice run through the defense inside the 6-yard box.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
