<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>shin kong on Taipei City FC Test Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/shin-kong/</link>
    <description>Recent content in shin kong on Taipei City FC Test Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 03:12:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/shin-kong/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cushty against Mitsukoshi</title>
      <link>http://example.org/cushty-against-mitsukoshi-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 03:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/cushty-against-mitsukoshi-2/</guid>
      <description>Time: 7pm, March 24th, 2012 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie In unseasonably cold weather, Taipei City took on Mitsukoshi in the first game of the weekend double-header. Rightly concentrating on the here and now, Dan Calvert asked his squad before kick-off to forget about Fritz the next day and just do their best to beat Mitsukoshi, a team capable of surprises. Dan named a 4-4-2 formation of Dale Neal in goal; Ricardo Abrego, Brian McGuinness, Tom Clarke and ‘Dapper’ Danny Wilkinson at the back; Danny Weir, Ebu Njie, debutant Michael Crossley and Omar Malcolm in midfield; and, Brian Fitzpatrick and Dan Calvert up front.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Murphy Brace, City Bend But Don&#39;t Break</title>
      <link>http://example.org/murphy-brace-city-bend-but-dont-break/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2010 06:01:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/murphy-brace-city-bend-but-dont-break/</guid>
      <description>Time: 3pm, January 31st, 2010 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Ed Cartee The win streak is still intact as Taipei City make a run for the BML title, despite City not being their usual selves on this day. The weather was decently hot, especially in contrast to the cooler temperatures in recent weeks, and many of City&amp;rsquo;s players weren&amp;rsquo;t totally fresh since they had already played a full game earlier in the day for their CPL teams.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
