<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Uncategorized on Taipei City FC Test Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/uncategorized/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Uncategorized on Taipei City FC Test Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2012 13:36:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/uncategorized/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dale Saves City at the Death</title>
      <link>http://example.org/dale-saves-city-at-the-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2012 13:36:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/dale-saves-city-at-the-death/</guid>
      <description>Gathering at a rain-sodden Da Jia pitch on a blustery, cold day, while the Peacock opposition waited in their cars, Dan announced a 4-4-2 formation of Dale in goal, Matt Wharton at right-back and Dapper Wilkinson at left-back, with Alastair Frost and Alan Murray providing the bolster in central defence. In midfield Danny Weir on the right and Luis Mayorga on the left provided thrust, while Ebu fed and Christie sat in central midfield; up front Alex schemed in the hole behind Malcolm as the last man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Does It Mean To Miss Against Mitsukoshi?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/what-does-it-mean-to-miss-against-mitsukoshi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2012 14:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/what-does-it-mean-to-miss-against-mitsukoshi/</guid>
      <description>The opening games of a new football season always throw up difficult questions for football teams. Sunday’s game against Mitsukoshi asked a lot of questions of City, and we will have to wait a little longer to see if this season’s group of Taipei City players has the answers. Conceding one early goal might be considered unlucky, but conceding two definitely asks questions! There was a general lassitude running all the way through the team in that first half hour that can only be described as pathetic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Dent Dentway in Season Opener</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-dent-dentway-in-season-opener/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2012 13:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-dent-dentway-in-season-opener/</guid>
      <description>Time: 1pm, Oct 28th, 2012 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie On a dry pitch sprinkled in misty drizzle, City met Dentway in the opening game of the BML. It was the first game of the season and it showed! A very fast, skiddy surface meant that it was a day for passing strictly to feet. Sadly, lateness was possibly one more factor in City&amp;rsquo;s failure to open their season in tip-top form!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Prevail in Weekend Double Header</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-prevail-in-weekend-double-header/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2012 08:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-prevail-in-weekend-double-header/</guid>
      <description>Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie Two games in two days is not recommended for a footballer&amp;rsquo;s health or for his play, yet, with four games left to play and firmly seated in the driver&amp;rsquo;s seat with all eyes on the prize of the BML Title, that was what was required of Taipei City against the rookie boys of San Chung High School on Saturday, May 12th and against the redoubtable Red Lions on Sunday, May 13th.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peacocks and City Share the Points</title>
      <link>http://example.org/peacocks-and-city-share-the-points/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 03:44:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/peacocks-and-city-share-the-points/</guid>
      <description>Time: 3pm, April 15th, 2012 Venue: Da Jia Yingfeng Riverside Park By Michael Christie In their previous match, City beat the Peacocks through a Brian Fitzpatrick goal. The Peacocks had given City a really tough game, and probably deserved a draw. This time, on a windy, overcast but still overly warm Taiwanese April day at Da Jia Riverside Park, the Peacocks gave City a similarly tough game. City had not played for three weeks, which is a long time when it comes to playing football.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cushty against Mitsukoshi</title>
      <link>http://example.org/cushty-against-mitsukoshi-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 03:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/cushty-against-mitsukoshi-2/</guid>
      <description>Time: 7pm, March 24th, 2012 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie In unseasonably cold weather, Taipei City took on Mitsukoshi in the first game of the weekend double-header. Rightly concentrating on the here and now, Dan Calvert asked his squad before kick-off to forget about Fritz the next day and just do their best to beat Mitsukoshi, a team capable of surprises. Dan named a 4-4-2 formation of Dale Neal in goal; Ricardo Abrego, Brian McGuinness, Tom Clarke and ‘Dapper’ Danny Wilkinson at the back; Danny Weir, Ebu Njie, debutant Michael Crossley and Omar Malcolm in midfield; and, Brian Fitzpatrick and Dan Calvert up front.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
