<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>vs. Hong Min Bulien on Taipei City FC Test Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/vs.-hong-min-bulien/</link>
    <description>Recent content in vs. Hong Min Bulien on Taipei City FC Test Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 05:17:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/vs.-hong-min-bulien/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>City Fight to the Draw</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-fight-to-the-draw/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2012 05:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-fight-to-the-draw/</guid>
      <description>Time: 3pm, May 20th, 2012 Venue: BaiLing Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie A single point would be enough to claim a third BML Championship, but against Bulien anything might happen and what a day for a football match! On a waterlogged pitch fit only for crabs, ducks and other wildlife, Taipei City took on an old bete noire in an ugly-tempered game. The weather, pitch and the football were all equally ugly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taipei Overcome Toughest Hurdle Yet</title>
      <link>http://example.org/taipei-overcome-toughest-hurdle-yet-comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 07:46:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/taipei-overcome-toughest-hurdle-yet-comments/</guid>
      <description>biuro-rachunkowe-warszawa.biz.pl - Sep 6, 2014
Providing you are a Director or employee of a company, these payments are an allowable deduction against the Corporation tax liability of the company. The Authority - Any one who has legal power over you is the Authority. For example, if your business is into plants, then you can have a Venus fly trap design for your folded business card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taipei Overcome Toughest Hurdle Yet</title>
      <link>http://example.org/taipei-overcome-toughest-hurdle-yet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 07:46:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/taipei-overcome-toughest-hurdle-yet/</guid>
      <description>Time: 7pm, March 17th, 2012 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie As usual against Hong Ming Bulien, Taipei City did not enjoy the best preparation in the critical hour leading up to the kick-off. Several players struggled to arrive in time, but Taipei City still had a good eleven ready to start, and of course an exceptionally strong bench. The 4-4-2 formation comprised Dale Neal in goal; a back line of Ricardo Abrego, Brian McGuinness, Tom Clarke and Mamadi Colley; a midfield quartet of Danny Weir, Oumar Senoussi, Michael Christie and Omar Malcolm; and a front pairing of Brian Fitzpatrick and Neo King.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Pipped at the Post</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-pipped-at-the-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2011 06:28:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-pipped-at-the-post/</guid>
      <description>Time: 6pm, March 19th, 2011 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie With everything to play for, both Taipei City and Hong Ming Bualien lined up to contest the game of the season – the BML final in all but name. Taipei City started with a 4-4-2 formation: Dale Neal in goal, Yunusa Njie at right-back, Ross Conlon at left-back, Brian McGuinness and Tom Clarke in central defense, Carlos Mayorga at right-midfield, Alex Ramirez at left-midfield, Ebrima Njie and Badou Njie in central midfield, and Dawda Fatty and Dan Calvert up front, Dawda in the hole and Dan as the target man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Season So Far</title>
      <link>http://example.org/the-season-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 08:37:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/the-season-so-far/</guid>
      <description>By Michael Christie After twelve games played, with ten victories, one draw and one defeat, Taipei City face into the penultimate game of the BML season in top spot. So, how has the season actually progressed for Taipei City so far…? Read on… Game 1: An Easy Opener against JFC Taipei City was lucky to have their easiest game of the season first. New to the BML, JFC strangely decided to field a weak team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Threadbare Blues have enough for Bulien</title>
      <link>http://example.org/threadbare-blues-have-more-than-enough-for-bulien/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2010 05:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/threadbare-blues-have-more-than-enough-for-bulien/</guid>
      <description>Time: 10am, January 17th, 2010 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By John Phillips An understrength Taipei City side overcame a spirited performance by Bulien to maintain their challenge for a second BML crown. In the end the scoreline flattered Bulien who scored their second goal with the final kick of the game and never looked likely to upset a well-drilled City side. Missing regular starters Calvert, Ramirez, Christie, Conlon, the Njie trio and both goalkeepers through a mixture of injury, suspension and other commitments, City shuffled their pack but still had enough firepower to see off a Bulien team that worked hard but rarely threatened from open play.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
