<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>vs. Fritz Air on Taipei City FC Test Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/vs.-fritz-air/</link>
    <description>Recent content in vs. Fritz Air on Taipei City FC Test Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 08:37:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/vs.-fritz-air/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Season So Far</title>
      <link>http://example.org/the-season-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 08:37:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/the-season-so-far/</guid>
      <description>By Michael Christie After twelve games played, with ten victories, one draw and one defeat, Taipei City face into the penultimate game of the BML season in top spot. So, how has the season actually progressed for Taipei City so far…? Read on… Game 1: An Easy Opener against JFC Taipei City was lucky to have their easiest game of the season first. New to the BML, JFC strangely decided to field a weak team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Champions Prove their Point</title>
      <link>http://example.org/the-champions-prove-their-point/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2010 04:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/the-champions-prove-their-point/</guid>
      <description>Time: 10am, March 21st, 2010 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie On a warm morning, with a sandstorm blowing in from Mainland China, Taipei City faced Fritz Air in their penultimate game this season. Missing their influential contingent of Gambian students, City nevertheless assembled a strong eleven, albeit without regular goalkeeper, Dale (who turned up after the final whistle), obliging Spencer to put on the keeper&amp;rsquo;s jersey and gloves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Make Light Work of Air</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-make-light-work-of-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2009 09:47:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-make-light-work-of-air/</guid>
      <description>On a cold morning,Taipei City engaged with a depleted Fritz Air team. The kick-off was put back thirty minutes to allow enough Fritz Air players to get out of bed. This was frustrating for City given that everybody had assembled right on time. Dawda led an excellent warm-up at 9.45, but the game started at about 10.30. When the game finally started, City fielded an exceptionally strong eleven against a team of eight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taipei City ground Fritz Air</title>
      <link>http://example.org/taipei-city-ground-fritz-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2009 14:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/taipei-city-ground-fritz-air/</guid>
      <description>On a surprisingly cloudy day, Taipei City assembled a surprisingly small squad to give Fritz Air a surprisingly good game. Played on Bai Ling B, the surface was uneven in places but still allowed for good football. With several defensive specialists missing, the Taipei City starting line-up looked attack top-heavy. The biggest shock saw Dan Calvert play as the sweeper. (Yes, that&amp;rsquo;s Dan Calvert playing as the sweeper!) With the ever-reliable Sam in goal and John and Christie either side, the defence was by no means weak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fritz Air No Match for Taipei City</title>
      <link>http://example.org/fritz-air-no-match-for-taipei-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 16:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/fritz-air-no-match-for-taipei-city/</guid>
      <description>Coming into the game after a surprising loss to the Red Lions, Taipei City had to muster up a fighting spirit to defeat Fritz Air. Final score 4-0 for Taipei City with goals coming from Dan Calvert, Gustavo Lopez, Chris Grimaud, and Spencer Pangborn. [caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_117&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;500&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Lining up against the air shipping division of the Fritz Company&amp;rdquo;][/caption] [caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_118&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;500&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Gustavo Lopez and the 2-0 scoreboard&amp;rdquo;][/caption] [caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_119&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;500&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Dawda makes a pass forward&amp;rdquo;][/caption]</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
