<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>vs. Dentway on Taipei City FC Test Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/vs.-dentway/</link>
    <description>Recent content in vs. Dentway on Taipei City FC Test Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 08:37:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/vs.-dentway/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Season So Far</title>
      <link>http://example.org/the-season-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2011 08:37:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/the-season-so-far/</guid>
      <description>By Michael Christie After twelve games played, with ten victories, one draw and one defeat, Taipei City face into the penultimate game of the BML season in top spot. So, how has the season actually progressed for Taipei City so far…? Read on… Game 1: An Easy Opener against JFC Taipei City was lucky to have their easiest game of the season first. New to the BML, JFC strangely decided to field a weak team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amateur Soccer Leagues set for Thrilling Finales</title>
      <link>http://example.org/amateur-soccer-leagues-set-for-thrilling-finales/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 05:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/amateur-soccer-leagues-set-for-thrilling-finales/</guid>
      <description>By John Phillips Taipei Times Saturday, Mar 13, 2010 At least one of Taipei’s amateur soccer leagues will be decided tomorrow as Da-an face the Red Lions needing to win by at least three clear goals to snatch the Carnegies Premier League (CPL) title at 1pm at Taipei’s Dajia Riverside Park. Across the city at Shilin’s Bai­ling Bridge at 4pm, expat team Taipei City can take a huge step toward clinching their second Businessman’s League (BML) trophy when they take on Sanchung High School.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dentway Gets a Drilling</title>
      <link>http://example.org/dentway-gets-a-drilling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 17:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/dentway-gets-a-drilling/</guid>
      <description>Time: 3pm, December 6th, 2009 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie On a warm and sunny day, Taipei City easily overcame the resistance offered by Dentway but only came away with five goals. The first clean sheet of the season was possibly more important than the margin of victory, if City can build on this performance. The first half started with Alex Moga in goal; a back three of Matt Wharton, Tim Murphy and John Phillips; a five-man midfield of Spencer Pangborn and Stevey Reymond on the right and left flanks, and Oliver Harley, Michael Christie and Ebrima Njie in the middle; and, a forward pairing of Dawda Fatty and Dan Calvert.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
