<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>San Chong on Taipei City FC Test Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/san-chong/</link>
    <description>Recent content in San Chong on Taipei City FC Test Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 May 2012 08:56:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/san-chong/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>City Prevail in Weekend Double Header</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-prevail-in-weekend-double-header/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2012 08:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-prevail-in-weekend-double-header/</guid>
      <description>Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie Two games in two days is not recommended for a footballer&amp;rsquo;s health or for his play, yet, with four games left to play and firmly seated in the driver&amp;rsquo;s seat with all eyes on the prize of the BML Title, that was what was required of Taipei City against the rookie boys of San Chung High School on Saturday, May 12th and against the redoubtable Red Lions on Sunday, May 13th.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Overpower the San Chung Boys</title>
      <link>http://example.org/city-overpower-the-san-chung-boys/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 03:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/city-overpower-the-san-chung-boys/</guid>
      <description>Time: 3pm, January 15th, 2012 Venue:BaiLingBridgeRiversidePark By Michael Christie On a treacherous pitch inimical to the stylish kind of game Taipei City aspires to, the boys of San Chung Senior High were looking for an upset. In the end, though, while they showed clever footwork and some pace, they lacked strength. A solid if unspectacular performance from City was enough. Dan started with a back line of Dale Neal in goal, Matt Wharton at right-back, Brian McGuinness and Tom Clarke in central defense, and Oumar Yassouf at left-back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Chong Raise Their Level But City Overcomes</title>
      <link>http://example.org/san-chong-raise-their-level-but-city-overcomes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2010 03:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/san-chong-raise-their-level-but-city-overcomes/</guid>
      <description>Time: 1pm, March 14th, 2010 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Ed Cartee With 3 games left in the season, City knew that 2 wins would clinch the BML title; but the way to that goal lay first through the San Chong boys, one of the more impressive possession-oriented sides in the rest of the league, so City had to be fully focused and honed in on the 90 minutes before them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amateur Soccer Leagues set for Thrilling Finales</title>
      <link>http://example.org/amateur-soccer-leagues-set-for-thrilling-finales/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 05:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/amateur-soccer-leagues-set-for-thrilling-finales/</guid>
      <description>By John Phillips Taipei Times Saturday, Mar 13, 2010 At least one of Taipei’s amateur soccer leagues will be decided tomorrow as Da-an face the Red Lions needing to win by at least three clear goals to snatch the Carnegies Premier League (CPL) title at 1pm at Taipei’s Dajia Riverside Park. Across the city at Shilin’s Bai­ling Bridge at 4pm, expat team Taipei City can take a huge step toward clinching their second Businessman’s League (BML) trophy when they take on Sanchung High School.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Chong Salvage Point</title>
      <link>http://example.org/san-chong-salvage-point/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2009 07:09:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/san-chong-salvage-point/</guid>
      <description>Time: 1pm, December 13th, 2009 Venue: Bai Ling Bridge Riverside Park By Michael Christie On an extremely hot day, with the sun beating down from a high place, Taipei City kicked off against San Chong. Ross had warned everybody before the game that San Chong had recently strung together some good results against the better sides in the league, so they would not be the pushovers remembered from previous seasons. He was right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No tie for San Chong this time</title>
      <link>http://example.org/san-chong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2009 15:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/san-chong/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this season the San Chong High School team put up a good challenge to Taipei City, forcing a 1-1 tie. City came out stronger this time, showing the quality of football that the fan(s) have come to expect from the BML champions. Starting off with only 10 men on the field, City went down and scored even though the numbers were against them. Dan Calvert put away a nice goal early on, 1-0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Match against San Chong ends in a draw</title>
      <link>http://example.org/match-against-san-chong-ends-in-a-draw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2009 16:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/match-against-san-chong-ends-in-a-draw/</guid>
      <description>The first game of 2009 started rough with only 10 men on the pitch, but 3 minutes into the game Taipei City had a full squad. The young San Chong team came out fast and scored 20 minutes into the game. Later in the first half Steve equalized with a clean put-away in the bottom corner, tying the game at 1-1. City started the 2nd half strong with good defense from Chris and solid offensive advances from Alex R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taipei City Continues 8-Game Winning Streak</title>
      <link>http://example.org/taipei-city-continues-8-game-winning-streak/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2008 15:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/taipei-city-continues-8-game-winning-streak/</guid>
      <description>After a slow start to the season, at one point resting 6th out of 8 teams, Taipei City FC has clawed its way back to the top of the BML standings. This past weekend Taipei City posted wins over Jako FC and SanChong High School. These 2 victories helped extend City&amp;rsquo;s current winning streak to 8 games. Here is the match report by team captain Dan Calvert. Here are a few pics from Saturday&amp;rsquo;s match.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
